几周前
A few weeks ago,
一个隐形穹顶罩住了切斯特磨坊镇
an invisible dome crashed down on Chester's Mill,
使我们与世隔绝
cutting us off from the rest of the world.
为什么穹顶会在这里  以后还会有什么谜团
Why the dome is here or what mysteries lie ahead,
我们依然一无所知
we still don't know.
每天它都考验我们的极限
Every day it tests our limits,
激发我们内心最善和最恶一面
bringing out the best and the worst in us.
有人说我们会永远困在这里
Some say we'll be stuck here forever,
但我们会一直奋力寻找出路
but we will never stop fighting to find a way out.
你杀了你侄子爱过的一个19岁的姑娘
You killed a 19-year-old girl that your nephew loved!
我必须如此
I had to!
我需要给里面的一个人传个消息
I need to get a message to somebody on the inside.
不如你把你想说的话
Why don't you write down what you want to say
还有要发的地址写下来
and where you want to send it.
记得把蛋带上
"So get the egg and bring it with you."
天呐  他真的给我改了
Oh, my God. He did change it.
你现在相信我了
Now do you believe me?
我爸爸要那颗蛋干什么
What does my dad want with the egg?
不能让别人知道芭比的事
No one can know about Barbie.
你是担心大个儿吉姆
You're worried about Big Jim.
芭比不在了  指不定他会做什么
Without Barbie, there's no telling what he'll do.
芭比又给你发了一封邮件
Barbie sent you another e-mail.
他还活着
He's alive.
所以你要跳下去吗
So you're gonna jump?
不  他不想我这么做
No. He doesn't want me to.
别跳
Don't jump!
放开他  芭比
Leave him alone! Barbie!
这是哪里
Where am I?
别紧张
Relax.
绝对安全
Perfectly safe.
只要你肯说出来
As long as you talk.
我很乐意说出来
I'm happy to.
我要打个电话
My one phone call.
我们不是警察
We're not the police.
也不是军队
Or the military.
你们穿着黑色制服  没有徽章
You got black uniforms, no insignias...
没有标志旗
no flag of origin.
那违反了《日内瓦公约》
That's a violation of Geneva Convention.
说了有人因携带虚假证件
Says the man who was caught trespassing
擅自闯入受限安全区域被捕
in a restricted security zone with false credentials.
好吧  要么控告我  要么让我走
Okay, so charge me or let me go.
《国防授权法案》里面写着
National Defense Authorization Act says
我不用控告你或是释放你
I don't have to charge you or release you.
-我不是恐怖分子  -证明啊
- I'm not a terrorist. - Prove it.
告诉我为什么你昨晚要去穹顶
Tell me why you went to the dome last night.
去死吧
Go to hell.
我们盯上过你
We've had our eye on you.
戴尔·芭芭拉  特种部队
Dale Barbara, Special Forces.
那你知道所有的事了
So you know it all.
我不明白你还想从我这里知道些什么
I don't know what else you need from me.
你怎么从切斯特磨坊镇出来的
How'd you get out of Chester's Mill?
我要知道精确路线
I want the exact route.
你说  别跳
"Don't jump," you said.
为什么你要对那个女人
Why'd you tell that woman,
茱莉亚·沙姆韦  说不要跳
Julia Shumway, not to jump?
你为什么要关心我是怎么或是为什么出来的
What do you care how or why I got out?
因为你们同心协力要拯救里面的人吗
'Cause you're so gung ho to save everyone on the inside?
你他妈做了什么拯救我们的事
What the hell have you done to help any of us?
你得合作
You're going to cooperate.
包括让沙姆韦女士交出那能量源
Including getting Ms. Shumway to hand over that power source.
原来是这个目的
So this is about that.
你承认了你知道那是什么了
You admit you know what it is.
是的  我知道
Well, yeah.
我只是知道你永远得不到你想要的东西
I just think that you want something you're never gonna get.
有本事别改变主意  耍聪明的家伙
Hold that thought, smart guy.
早上好  茱莉亚
Good morning, Julia.
吉姆
Hey, Jim.
在享受当上警长的第一天吗
Enjoying your first day as sheriff?
是啊  玩得很开心
Oh, yeah, having a blast.
这些天从来不缺少麻烦
Never a shortage of trouble these days.
说到这个  我开车路过发现
Speaking of which, I was driving by and I noticed that...
又有一些家伙在外面了
you got some company again out there.
这几星期都没有近距离看到守卫了
Haven't seen guards this close in weeks.
知道他们在那里干什么吗
Any idea what they're doing there?
不知道
No.
那你最近也没看到什么奇怪的事情吗
So you haven't seen anything odd lately?
穹顶之外
Outside the dome?
我和你一样困惑
I'm as stumped as you are.
如果你看到什么不寻常的事
Well, if you do see anything unusual,
用我给你的对讲机联系我
just give me a call on that walkie I gave you.
肯定很难有解脱感
Must be hard getting a sense of closure.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我的意思是没有机会埋葬芭比
I mean not getting a chance to bury Barbie.
我妻子死的时候  事故非常严重
When my wife died, the accident was severe.
没法瞻仰遗容  那是封闭的棺材
There was no viewing. It was a closed casket.
不论如何  我只是想说
Anyways... what I'm trying to say is
如果你要我组织一队人
if you want me to organize a team
去帮忙搜寻尸体
to help recover the body...
好让你有机会说再见
give you a chance to say good-bye....
你真好心
Well, that's kind of you,
但我不想让任何人陷入危险
but I wouldn't want to put anyone else in danger.
这也是芭比为了山姆所做的事
That's what Barbie was doing for Sam,
看看结果怎么样吧
and look how that turned out.
如果你改变主意
If you change your mind,
跟警长说
give the sheriff a holler.
会的
Will do.
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：加森   圈圈   面条   michael   roaddog   冰蓝
■
校对：冰蓝     时间轴：加森   大喷子   小雨
后期：冰蓝     总监：冰蓝
■
你觉得他知道了吗
Do you think he knows?
关于芭比还活着吗
About Barbie being alive?
他问了好多问题
He was asking a lot of questions.
这正是为什么我们得保守秘密
Exactly why we have to keep this to ourselves
直到我们知道芭比没事
until we know he's okay.
他可能发了另一封邮件
He might send another e-mail.
恐怕他们不会让他发的
Doubt they'll let him.
也许抓走芭比的人
Maybe the guys who took Barbie
正是想要蛋的那些人
are the same ones who want the egg.
他们怎么知道那个蛋的
How would they even know about it?
更应该问的是
Better question is,
他们拿到蛋会干什么
what would they do if they got a hold of it?
你不会把蛋给他们吧
Well, you wouldn't give the egg to them.
我们会保护它  对吧
We'll protect it, right?
除非我知道芭比安全了
Until I know Barbie's safe,
否则我也不知道该怎么办
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
我们回学校碰碰运气
Let's get back to the school on the off chance
看看他有没有再发邮件来
he does get another e-mail through.
好主意
That's a good idea.
我要回警局
Listen, I'm gonna head back to the station
看着我爸
and keep an eye on my dad.
为什么是红色  为什么是一扇门
Why red? Why a door?
《旧约》里写到
You know, i-in the Old Testament,
以色列人会以羔羊之血
the Israelites would paint their doors red
把自己家的门涂成红色作为祭祀的标志
with the blood of lambs as a symbol of sacrifice
那样复仇天使就会绕过他们
so that the angel of vengeance would pass them by.
你真会讲故事啊  对不对
Oh, you're just full of happy stories, aren't you?
山姆  别老跟他对着干  艺术基本理论
Sam, give him a break. Art theory 101--
一扇门总是代表通向什么地方的一条路
a door always symbolizes a way in somewhere.
你看  那个储物柜
Hey, look-- the locker, right?
学校里面那个
In the school?
我通过那个储物柜离开的切斯特磨坊镇
I went through that to get out of Chester's Mill.
也就是说这扇门可能是入口  不管它在哪里
So, this door could be a way back in-- wherever it is.
我跳下悬崖后
When I went off the cliff,
醒来时是在游乐场里
I woke up in some kids' playground.
我也是这样
That's exactly what happened to me.
你在游乐场那边看到了红色的门吗
Did you see a red door at the playground?
没注意
Didn't notice.
那如果这扇门真的通往切斯特磨坊镇
So, if this door does lead to Chester's Mill,
我就有可能通过它找到小詹姆斯
it could be a way for me to get Junior
然后把他带来这里
and bring him back here.
你要把吉姆也带出来吗
Are you gonna bring Jim back, too?
现在我没时间考虑这个
I can't think about that right now.
我们先去游乐场看看那里有没有红色的门吧
Let's go to the playground and see if there's a red door there.
你去哪里了  詹姆斯
Where you been, James?
就到处看看
Just... making rounds.
看到穹顶外面的人了吗
See all that activity outside the dome?
穿黑衣的那帮人
Fellas in black?
看到了
Yeah, I did.
昨晚我还看到了别人
I saw someone else, too, last night
在穹顶外面
on the other side.
谁
Who?
芭比
Barbie.
他还活着
He's alive.
你知道吗
Did you know?
我知道  爸爸
Yeah, Dad. I did.
谢谢你跟我说实话  儿子
Well, thank you for being honest with me, son.
我需要你继续对我诚实
Now, I need you to keep being honest with me.
我需要你给我看一样东西
There's something I want you to show me.
你有两分钟时间
You got two minutes.
戴尔  你没事吧
Dale, are you okay?
你是指除了我手上的手铐还有这里
Oh, what-- you mean aside from the bracelets
"奢华"的住宿条件之外吗
and the luxury accommodations?
你怎么进来的
How did you get in here?
我动用了自己的一切关系
I pulled every string I have.
那就再多动用点把我救出去
So then pull a few more and get me out.
戴尔  我是开能源公司的
Dale, I run an energy company.
我的朋友都是在特区那边坐办公室的
The friends I have sit in offices in D.C.
至于其他人  他们...
These other people, they're...
他们是另一伙人
they're something else.
你不知道他们是什么人吗
But you don't know who?
几周前用导弹攻击穹顶失败以后
After the failed missile strike on the dome a couple weeks ago,
国会和媒体都狠狠训斥了他们一番
they caught hell from congress, the media.
可能他们只是为了让自己远离目前的情况
Probably just trying to distance themselves from the situation.
所以就雇佣了私人承包商
So they hired private contractors.
就跟政府雇你来负责
Kind of how the government hired you to handle
跟穹顶那边的一切通讯一样
all the communication to the dome.
你告诉我  是谁更改了我发给茱莉亚的信息
So, tell me-- who changed my message to Julia?
是你还是他们
Was that you or was that them?
我想帮你把信息发过去
I tried to get it through.
但是他们发现了  还用暴力威胁我
But they caught me and they strong-armed me.
为了把你的信息发给茱莉亚
In order to send your message to Julia,
他们坚持要加上点关于那颗蛋的...
they insisted that we add the bit about the egg...
爸爸  别说了
Dad! Stop!
好吗  够了  不要骗我了
All right? Enough. No more lies!
儿子  我想救你出去
Son, I want you out of those cuffs.
唯一渺茫的机会就是  你得说服茱莉亚
The only way there's a ghost chance of that happening is
把那颗蛋带出来
you have to convince Julia to bring the egg.
只有那个才足够换取
It's the only thing that's valuable enough
你的自由
to trade for your release.
我帮不了你
I can't help you.
你还是这么固执
You're still so damn stubborn.
希望这件事最后不会把我们俩都害死
I just hope it doesn't end up getting us both killed.
时间到了
Time's up.
你尽力了  先生
You tried, sir.
可是你没有尽力
And you're not trying hard enough.
如果无法保证一件东西的安全
What's the point of owning a security firm
那开安全公司有什么用
if it can't secure a damn thing?
很快军方就会发现
It won't be long before the military
穹顶的能量源了
really does find out about the power source.
所以
So...
要使用一切可能的方法吗
by any means necessary?
不惜一切代价
Whatever it takes.
看上去好像没有尽头
Looks like there's no end to it.
芭比就是从这里出去的对吧
This is how Barbie got out, huh?
难以置信
Hard to believe.
这个无法解释  爸爸
You can't explain it, Dad.
你只能接受现实
You just have to accept it.
要坚持信念
Take it on faith.
什么
What?
你母亲去世前
It was everything your mother
一直在说这个
said before she died.
我之前认为那一切都很疯狂
Everything I thought was so crazy.
可能现在一切都开始有意义了
Maybe it's all starting to make sense now.
-你从未相信过她  -我无法相信
- And you never believed her. - Well, I couldn't.
直到现在
Till now.
直到我亲眼看到这一切
With all this staring me in the face.
真希望能有机会向她道歉
I just wish I could apologize.
因为曾质疑她
For doubting her.
我想为了再见到她
I guess we'd both give anything
我们都会不惜一切代价  对吧
to see her again, huh?
昨天
Yesterday...
你说是穹顶选择了你
you said the dome chose you.
穹顶对你有安排
That it had a plan for you.
就是这个
This is it.
我的任务就是
It's my job
带领这镇上的人民重获自由
to lead the people of this town to freedom.
-你说芭比是从这里跳下去的  -对
- You said Barbie jumped here, right? - Yeah.
但昨晚  在穹顶外
But last night, outside the dome,
当他看到茱莉亚时  告诉她不要跳
when he saw Julia, he told her not to jump.
-他说原因了吗  -没有
- He say why? - No.
她认为把他抓走的那些人想要那颗蛋
She thinks that the guys who dragged him off want the egg.
蛋
The egg?
我以为她已经扔了那玩意儿
I thought she got rid of that thing.
她试过
She tried to.
那东西好像有自己的思想
The thing kind of has a mind of its own.
而你们都认为是它给穹顶提供的能量
And you all think it powers the dome.
-这就是它的工作原理  对吧  -对
- That's the-the working theory, right? - Yeah.
我猜这就是那些警卫又回来的原因
I bet that's why those guards are back.
它现在在哪
Where is it now?
我不知道
I don't know.
作为这镇上仅有的两名警察
Well, as the only two lawmen left in this town,
我们最好把它找出来
we'd better track it down.
穹顶之下  第二季第九集
三年级时  詹姆斯每天都求我
Every day of the third grade, James would beg me
带他到学校后面的游乐场玩
to take him to the playground after school.
结果发现是因为那里有位金发小美女
Turns out there was this little blonde there.
叫安琪·麦卡利斯特
Angie McAlister.
他完全被她迷住了
He was infatuated with her.
有一天  他在她面前炫耀
One day, he was showing off for her,
他坐在跟那个一样的轮胎秋千上
he got in a tire swing just like that one,
他把绳子紧紧绕起来  然后开始旋转
and he wound it tight and he was spinning...
红门在那
There's the red door.
等等  等下  还有人盯着我们
Wait, wait, wait. We're not alone.
我去吸引那个拿平板电脑的人的注意
I'll try drawing off the one with the tablet.
你解决另外一个
You take the other one.
等你甩开他们后  我们在公园里的
Meet me back at the stone structure in the park
假山后面碰头
when you lose them.
大人不许玩
No grown-ups!
你想见我  先生
You wanted to see me, sir?
我们得再发条消息
We need to send another message.
向穹顶里
Into the dome?
我以为你说那会太显眼了
I... thought you said it was too conspicuous.
我以为你已经明白必须照我说的做
I thought you understood you do what I say.
还是说你之后想去蹲
Or your next stop will be whatever dark hole
联调局给商业间谍提供的大牢
the Feds throw punks who commit corporate espionage.
明白了  先生
Yes, sir.
我们在办公室会面吗
Should we meet back at the office?
我的电脑有远程登录界面
My computer has a remote interface.
就在这里做  马上
Do it from here. Now.
我们还要这样做多久
How long do we have to do this for?
连个信号都没有
There's not even a signal.
只有以前的旧邮件
Just these old e-mails.
茱莉亚不让我们停就不能停
As long as Julia wants us to.
万一芭比出了什么事呢
What if something bad's happened to Barbie?
乔  别这么说
Joe, don't say that.
我是说  也许我们应该跳下去
I mean, maybe we should jump.
他毕竟逃出去了
After all, he got out.
但他昨晚说外面不安全
And last night he said it's not safe out there.
那我们就在里面待一辈子吗
Do we just stay here forever, then?
在某种程度上  在外面不安全
At some point, "not safe" out there
可能要好过在里面不安全
might be better than "not safe" in here.
-有什么发现吗  -没有
- Anything? - Not yet.
快看
Look.
戴安娜的猎犬  刚看到了你的新视频
"戴安娜的猎犬"
"Hounds of Diana."
叫那个怪名字的人以前回过我的推特
Someone with that weird name posted on my Twitter.
看看那封邮件
Open that e-mail.
我们刚收到封新邮件
H-hey, we just got a new e-mail.
好奇怪
It's strange.
以前有无线网络信号的时候
Before, when the Wi-Fi signal was live,
收到过几封邮件
a few e-mails came through.
我觉得是发这封邮件的人控制着无线信号
Makes me think whoever's sending this is controlling the signal.
打开它
Open it.
致茱莉亚·沙姆韦
没有文字
No text.
只有个视频地址
It's just a video link.
是给你的  阿克泰昂能源发来的
For you, from Aktaion Energy.
茱莉亚
Julia.
我叫唐·芭芭拉
My name's Don Barbara.
是戴尔的父亲
I'm Dale's father.
我猜你更熟悉"芭比"这个名字
I think you know him as "Barbie."
那个声音
That voice...
我相信你一定很担心他
I'm sure you're concerned about him.
我认得那个声音
I know that voice.
他现在正被拘留
He's currently in custody
而且他天性使然
and, true to his nature,
一直拒绝合作
he's not cooperating.
现在  我并不想这么唐突
Now, I don't mean to be curt,
但我们时间不多了
but we don't have much time.
关押着他的那些人
The people who are holding him...
他们想要你们发现的
they want the power source
那个能量源
that you've discovered.
我听说你们叫它"蛋"
I understand you call it "The egg"?
他们想要研究它  弄明白它的机制
They want to study it, understand it.
它可能还是
It might even hold a key
救你们所有人出来的关键
to getting all of you out from under there.
这是唯一我所知的能换回戴尔自由的砝码
It's the only thing I know I can trade for Dale's release.
如果你不给他们
If you don't, I...
我不知道他们会对他做什么
I don't know what they may do to him.
所以求你了
So please,
请尽快
hurry.
我并不想以这种方式来见到
It's an unfortunate way to meet the woman
对我儿子如此重要的女人
who means so much to my son.
茱莉亚
Julia.
Julia!
怎么了
Yeah?
你打算怎么做
What are you gonna do?
那...
So...
我们继续刚才
how about we pick things up
没完成的事吧
where we left off?
你老爹也不会再来保护你了
And daddy's not here to protect you anymore.
这么打不公平
It's not really a fair fight.
没错
Yeah.
你高估我们了
Those are overrated.
现在
So...
你要让沙姆韦女士
you're gonna get Ms. Shumway
把那颗蛋交给我们
to deliver the egg to us.
好的
Yeah.
只要...
Just as long...
听不清你说的话  芭芭拉
Can't hear you, Barbara.
只要你
as you
去死吧
kiss my ass.
你打算什么时候告诉我
When were you gonna tell me?
我不喜欢被试探  吉姆
I've never liked fishing, Jim.
关于芭比的事
About Barbie.
芭比什么事
What about Barbie?
我昨晚看到他了  在穹顶外面
I saw him last night, outside the dome.
芭比还活着
Barbie's alive?
你是说茱莉亚没告诉你吗
You telling me Julia didn't tell you?
-你们俩最近不是合作无间吗  -吉姆
- As closely as you've been working together lately? - Jim...
我真不知道
I had no idea.
这么说她也骗了你
So she lied to you, too?
不
No.
如果有能出去的办法
If there was a way out,
茱莉亚不会瞒着镇上的人的
Julia wouldn't keep it from the town.
为了救芭比她会的
She would to save Barbie.
警卫抓了他  把他带走了
The guards caught him and dragged him off.
穹顶外的某些人为了要拿到那颗蛋不择手段
Someone out there is playing hardball to get this egg.
什么蛋
What egg?
你还真被蒙在鼓里  是吧
You really are in the dark here, aren't you?
那是个类似能量源的东西
It's some kind of energy source.
孩子们说  是它给穹顶提供能量
The kids say it, it generates the dome.
他们一直和茱莉亚一起保护着它
They've been protecting it with Julia.
我觉得你能找到这东西在哪
I thought you could locate this thing, you know?
造个
Build a...
探测蛋的什么东西
egg detector or something, you know?
就像科学家那样
As a scientist.
想想办法
Figure it out.
我觉得有个更好的办法
I think there's a way to find it
比电线和胶带要可靠得多
that's more reliable than copper wire and duct tape.
乔
Joe.
不  不行
No. No, no.
他是跟他们一伙的
No, he's part of the problem.
他信任我
Well, he trusts me.
我可以试探一下
I can poke around.
他或许会告诉我们他们的秘密
He might let us in on their secret.
好吧  去办吧
All right, go ahead.
看看他会不会告诉你那东西在哪
See if you can get him to show you where this thing is.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
-你把那人甩开了吗  -我想是的
- Did you lose the guy? - Yeah, I guess.
暂时是吧
I mean, for now.
那扇红门通向什么地方吗
That red door lead anywhere?
游乐场可能是过来的路
The playground may be the way in,
但不是过去的路
it is not the way out.
波琳  你在干什么
Pauline, what are you doing?
开始了  莱尔
It's starting, Lyle.
我头脑中的那些画面就是这么开始的
This is how my visions start.
从泥巴里
In mud?
天上的云彩
Cloud shapes...
无论我走到哪里  都会看到不同的符号
I see symbols everywhere I turn, anything.
现在又成了螺旋形
And now it's in the form of a spiral.
-这是什么意思  -我不知道
- What's that mean? - I don't know.
可能切斯特磨坊镇要发生什么不好的事了
Maybe something bad about going to Chester's Mill.
不是你说想要进去的吗
I thought that was your idea.
我不是说我们不应该去
I'm not saying we shouldn't go.
我们必须得去
We have to.
只是这个螺旋...
There's just something about this spiral...
我不知道  它吓着我了
I don't know, it scares me.
不  你不需要害怕
No, you don't need to be afraid.
波琳  我们在一起
Pauline, we're together.
莱尔  说实话
Lyle, honestly,
-我得  -没关系
- I have to... - Never mind.
忘了我刚才说的话
Forget I said it.
你找到什么了吗
Hey, did you find anything?
没有  是死胡同
Nah, dead end.
我们该走了  那些人可能认出了我们
We should keep moving. Those guys probably ID'd us,
而且我觉得回你的公寓也不安全了
and I don't think it's safe to go back to your apartment.
我知道一个安全地方可以去
I know a safe place we can stay.
谁知道这些人是谁
Who knows who any of these people are?
我们不能就这么把蛋给他们
We can't just give them the egg!
芭比可能有生命危险
Barbie's life could be at stake.
但是他告诉过你
But he told you
外面不安全
it's not safe out there!
你什么时候有投票权了
Since when do you even have a vote?
你难道不想出去吗  梅兰妮
Don't you want to get out, Melanie?
如果我们把蛋交给他们  我们就都能出去了
Look, if we give them the egg, then we can all escape.
我也可以再见到我父母了
I could see my parents again.
求你了  茱莉亚
Please, Julia.
你总是说穹顶是来保护我们的
You've always said that the dome is here to protect us.
它没有保护我妈妈
It didn't protect my mom.
还有我姐姐
Or my sister.
梅兰妮  我知道我说过什么
Melanie, I know what I said.
但是  悬崖和隧道可能...
But maybe the cliffs, the tunnels...
那都是穹顶在告诉我们
they're all the dome's way of telling us
发生了新情况
something new.
我们得离开
That we need to leave.
-或者把蛋交出去  -不行
- Or send the egg over. - No.
我因为这蛋死过一次
I died once for the egg
它又把我救了回来
and then it brought me back.
我不知道为什么  但我心里
I don't know why, but I feel in my heart
觉得我们得留着它
that we have to keep it with us.
好吧  你的感觉比救芭比的命
Okay, so your feeling's more important than keeping Barbie alive
和把我们弄出这个鬼地方还重要吗
and getting the rest of us out of this awful place?
你不知道自己在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about.
梅兰妮
Melanie!
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
我知道了
I know.
芭比没死
Barbie's alive.
那个蛋
The egg.
你瞒着我的所有事
Everything you've been keeping from me.
你偷听到的吗
Well, eavesdropping will do that.
实际上  是大个儿吉姆说的
Actually, Big Jim told me.
他知道了吗
He knows?
他想要蛋
And he wants the egg.
不  蛋到吉姆手里就完了
No, Jim having it would be a disaster.
所以我才来警告你
Which is why I came to warn you.
他派我来找到蛋在哪里  然后告诉他
He sent me to find out where it is and report back,
但我做不到
but I can't do that.
茱莉亚  我知道你不相信我
Julia, I know you don't trust me.
或许你有你的理由
It's probably with good reason,
但其实我和你一样
but the truth is I'm like you.
只是想救镇子
I just want to save the town.
所以你可以继续犹豫要不要相信我
So you can waste time trying to make your mind up about me,
或者接受我的帮助
or you can accept my help.
不管怎样
Either way,
这里的情况都还是会越来越糟的
things are going to get worse around here.
亨特  有人找你
Hunter, got some visitors for you.
波琳
Pauline.
接到你电话我还有点惊讶
I was kind of surprised to get your call.
我们只是要找个安全的地方待着
We just need a safe place to stay.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我都一周没你消息
I haven't talked to you in a week.
开始担心了
I was starting to get worried.
是  我一直在保持低调
Yeah, I've been lying low myself.
发现了穹顶的很多事
A lot of developments with the dome.
你不跟我们介绍下吗
Uh, you want to fill us in?
这是亨特  是我在齐尼斯高中
This is Hunter; he was my best student
教艺术时的得意门生
when I taught art at Zenith High.
那另外一位电脑天才呢
And this other computer gentleman?
特雷弗  戴安娜的猎犬的另一位成员
Trevor. Uh, another of the Hounds of Diana.
我们的网站基本像是个地下的信息源
Our web site's kind of an underground news source for everything
专门披露政府不想公布的穹顶消息
the government doesn't want people to know about the dome.
亨特  有人来了
Hunter, we got an incoming.
是游乐场那的人吗
Is that one of the guys from the playground?
-这里有后门吗  -只有前门
- Is there a back door? - Only the front one.
没事  特雷弗
It's okay, Trevor.
他就是这么打招呼的
It's kind of his way of saying hello.
怎么回事
What the hell?
你昨天去了穹顶边上吗
Did you get to the dome yesterday?
你个混蛋
Oh, you son of a bitch!
住手
Stop!
你是谁
Who are you?
她是我的朋友
She's a friend of mine.
波琳·维多
Pauline Verdreaux.
波琳·雷尼吗
Pauline Rennie?
你想把我弟弟怎么样
What do you want with my brother?
没事的  芭比
It's okay, Barbie.
我要想跑的话早就跑了
I would've run a while ago if I was going to.
那也不能帮你脱罪
That doesn't make you any less guilty.
-什么罪  -你弟弟是杀人凶手
- Guilty of what? - Your brother's a murderer.
他杀了安琪·麦卡利斯特
He killed Angie McAlister.
谁是管事的
我要跟他谈谈  马上
议员詹姆斯·雷尼  对吗
我能拿到你们要的
只跟我交易  不许跟别人
我要带所有人走
我和我儿子
把地点指给我看  我就给你
那是安琪的家
That's Angie's place.
我知道它在哪了
I know exactly where that's at.
我和我儿子
你杀了安琪吗
Did you kill Angie?
你的日记就像是说
Your journal made it seem like
穹顶是那四个孩子造成的
those four kids were somehow making it happen.
安琪  她弟弟乔
Angie, her brother Joe,
诺莉和小詹姆斯
Norrie and Junior.
告诉我
Tell me...
你没有动他一根汗毛
you did not touch a hair on his head.
当然没有  波琳
Of course not, Pauline.
天呐
Oh, my God.
怎么了
What?
所以我们得去那里
That's why we have to go there.
你看出来了吗
Don't you see?
因为我的画你杀了一个女孩
You killed that girl because of what I drew.
我们得去切斯特磨坊镇赎罪
We have to go to Chester's Mill to atone for our sins
否则不管我们去哪  都会良心不安
or we will never find peace, no matter where we run to.
你似乎挨了顿打啊  芭芭拉先生
You look a little banged up, Mr. Barbara.
惹错人了吗
You rub somebody the wrong way?
差不多吧
You might say that.
-你拿枪干什么  -别怕
- What is that for? - Hey, relax.
不是打你弟弟的
This isn't for your brother.
-还没到时候  -我没想跑  芭比
- Not yet. - I'm not running, Barbie.
我要回切斯特磨坊镇
I'm going back to Chester's Mill.
-我们都是  -什么
- We all are. - What?
-我得救詹姆斯出来  -是吗
- I have to get James out. - Oh, is that right?
我得救所有人出来
Well, I got to get everyone out.
问题是  怎么才能回去
Question is, how do you even get back in?
波琳又画了一幅画
Pauline did another drawing.
可能是回去的路
It may be a way back in.
不  不好意思  这些画可没
No, I'm sorry. These drawings have led
招来什么好东西
to some pretty awful stuff.
但这也不能改变
But it doesn't change the fact
我姐姐的画总是预言正确的事实
that my sister's drawings have always been right.
我们没必要走很远
We won't have to go far.
图像搜索发现了镇上的所有红门
An image search found possibilities in town.
这里有齐尼斯所有的红门
I've got all the red doors here in Zenith.
我个人觉得是贮藏室
Personally, I'm thinking the storage space,
但如果我们真的要挖掘时空
but if we're really digging into the space-time of it all,
殖民地银行里有《纳尼亚传奇》里的旋转门
the Colonial's got that whole Narnia spin.
你说你是在幻象中看到的吗
You said that you saw this in a vision?
它们总是有意义的
They always mean something.
我觉得那扇门是返回穹顶的方法
I think that door is the way back into the dome.
亨特  我们需要地址
Hunter, we need addresses.
不需要
No, you don't.
我知道这在哪里
I know where this is.
我在那里长大
I grew up there.
小詹姆斯  你要带它去哪里
Junior, where are you taking it?
我不能再把蛋放在安琪的公寓了
I can't keep the egg at Angie's apartment anymore.
那里不安全
It's not safe there.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我跟我爸爸说了
I told my dad about it.
-为什么  -我不知道
- Why? - I don't know.
他为切斯特磨坊镇做了很多好事
He's done a lot of good for Chester's Mill,
我告诉他这件事的那一秒...
and the moment I told him about it...
你就知道不该这样做吗
You knew you shouldn't have?
我知道很多人都不信任他
I know a lot of people don't trust him,
但我还在努力相信他
but I'm still trying to believe in him.
虽然他变得很糟糕
As messed up as it all is,
但我依然相信他曾是个好父亲
I still think he was a good father once.
我明白  但并不是所有父亲
I understand, but not all fathers
都能成为你想要他们成为的人
can be who you want them to be.
你在这里干什么  梅兰妮
What are you doing here, Melanie?
不止你爸爸一个人有理由拿走蛋
Your dad's not the only one with a reason to take the egg.
这段时间  我一直信任茱莉亚
I've had faith in Julia this whole time.
我依然努力去相信
I-I still try to have it,
但是我不确定了
but I don't know anymore.
我觉得她优先考虑的事变了
I think her priorities have shifted.
芭比现在对她更为重要
Barbie is more important to her now.
那她会用蛋来换他吗
So she's gonna trade the egg for him?
为了你爱的人  你不是也会这样做吗
Isn't that what you would do for the people you love?
在其他人看来很鲁莽的事
Things that seem reckless to everyone else?
并不是所有人都明白这点
Not everyone gets that.
并不是所有人都爱过
Not everyone's been in love.
从现在开始  你想跟我一起保护它吗
Do you want to protect it with me from now on?
我知道一个安全的地方
I know a place where we can keep it safe.
你对它做了什么
What did you do with it?
-什么  -我去了安琪的公寓
- Do with what? - I went to Angie's apartment,
现在蛋不见了
and now the egg is gone.
我觉得你知道蛋在那里
I think you knew it was there.
看来我们都被骗了
Looks like we both got skunked.
拜托
Come on.
你现在足够了解我  能看得出我是不是在撒谎
You know me well enough by now to tell when I'm lying.
因为例外非常罕见
Because the exception is so rare.
我不能因为丽贝卡
Well, I can't really get mad
跟你乱嚼舌根就生她的气
at Rebecca for flapping her lips at you.
大家都想要那个蛋
Everybody wants that damn thing.
但我想保护小镇  不止是芭比
But I'm trying to protect the town, not just Barbie.
芭比
Barbie?
他跟这事有什么关系
What does he have to do with this?
我们都知道芭比还活着
We both know Barbie's alive.
那些人抓到了他
Those men have him,
你打算给他们蛋
and you were gonna give them that egg
换取他的自由
to set him free.
这是个很大的风险
It's a pretty big risk.
我不指望你能理解
Well, I don't expect you to understand.
大个儿吉姆·雷尼不知道
Big Jim Rennie doesn't know what it's like
爱别人是什么感受
to love anyone other than himself.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
试试跟你儿子说
You try telling your boy
他妈妈不会再在放学后带他去公园玩了
that his mom's not gonna be taking him to the park anymore after school.
实际上  她不会回家了
In fact, she won't be coming home.
永远不会
Ever.
失去波琳对你俩来说一定不好受
I'm sure losing Pauline was incredibly hard for both of you.
我十分爱我的妻子  超出你的想象
I loved my wife more than you'll ever know.
我愿意付出一切  让她回来
And I'd give anything to have her back.
吉姆
Jim.
你为什么想要蛋
Why do you want the egg?
来拯救这座小镇
To save this town.
或者这只是另一个强权行为
Or maybe it's just another power play.
原来你不如我以为的那么了解我
Turns out you don't know me as well as I thought you did.
你没能让他吐出什么线索
And you couldn't get anything out of him?
什么也没有
Nothing.
跟梢有什么消息
Mm-hmm. Any word from the tail?
实际上  走了两个街区后  他原路折回
Actually two blocks away, he doubled back
然后他们跟丢了
and, well... he lost them.
什么
What?!
你说过这会管用的
You said this would work.
他会带我们去跟他出来的地方
That he would lead us somewhere related
有联系的地方
to where he came out.
我在尽快搜寻他的下落
I'm trying to reacquire his whereabouts as fast as possible.
外勤队给我发了条信息  说
And I got a message from our field team saying...
-闭嘴  -爸爸  我出来了
- Shut up. - Dad, I got out.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
该死
Damn it.
爸爸  我出来了  我需要你的帮助
Dad, I got out. I need your help.
红门在哪里
Where's the red door?
在后院的地窖  走吧
It's on a root cellar in the backyard. Come on.
地窖  那是什么
A root cellar? What the hell is that?
禁酒令下达后剩余的酒
Leftover from Prohibition.
这真是诡异的巧合啊
Weird coincidence, don't you think?
回切斯特磨坊镇的路就在你家
The way back to Chester's Mill being on your family's property?
如果你还相信巧合
If you still believe in coincidence,
那你根本就没用心
you're not paying attention.
来吧
Come on.
一个人刚给了我十块钱
Look, man, some guy just gave me ten bucks
让我来按门铃
to come ring the buzzer
-播放那段音频  -他是个诱饵
- and play that for you. - He's a decoy!
让他滚出这里
Get him the hell out of here!
现在就搜查这里
Have the grounds searched now.
有人入侵  进行搜查
Man of the breach, search the property.
那是我的手掌
That's mine.
门刷漆的那天印的
From the day it was painted.
快啊
All right, come on.
好了  我们走吧  走吧
All right, let's go, let's go.
快点  我们得走了
Come on, we got to go.
出什么事了
What's wrong?
-我不知道  我  -那边
- I don't know. I... - Over here!
你要么进去  要么被抓
Okay, either you go or you get caught.
你来选
It's your choice.
切斯特磨坊镇里的那条隧道
That tunnel that led us from Chester's Mill
隐藏在储物柜后面...
was hidden behind a locker or something...
是那个吗
Is that it?
之前根本没有这东西
That wasn't there before.
帮我搬开
Help me move some of these.
好吧
All right.
我们走吧
Let's go.
谢谢你帮我们来这里
Look, I appreciate all your help getting us here.
但我告诉你  你不会想这么做的
But I'm telling you, you don't want to do this.
除了波琳我没有别的熟人了
I-I got nobody here except Pauline.
你觉得你爸爸抓住我后会给我升职吗
And you think your dad's gonna give me a promotion if he catches me?
好吧  走吧
All right, go.
你在找什么呢
What are you looking for?
孩子
Oh, hey, kiddo.
我只是在找你妈妈的东西
I'm just looking for some of your mom's things.
我们一起带走的东西吗
Things to take with us?
我们一起带走
"Take with us"?
求你别留我跟我爸爸在一起
Please don't leave me here with my dad.
詹姆斯
Aw, James.
你爸爸会好好照顾你的
Your dad's gonna take good care of you.
别担心
Don't worry about that.
跟他好好照顾妈妈一样吗
The way he took good care of Mom?
对不起  孩子  我
I'm sorry, buddy, I-I...
我不能带走你
I can't take you with me.
那妈妈撒谎了
Then Mom lied.
关于什么
About what?
她说你有一天会救我
She said you were going to save me one day.
我还希望那是在今天
I-I was hoping that was today.
这会永远留在这里了
Now it'll be there forever.
以后你会看见  然后记起来你之前有多么小
So, one day you'll see it and remember how little you used to be.
你会在我长大之前回来吗
Will you come back before I grow big?
希望如此
I hope so.
你为什么就今天在这
Why are you only here today?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我妈妈想让我见你
But my mom wanted me to meet you.
以后我还会见到你的
And I'll see you again one day.
我保证
Promise.
搞什么
What the hell?
我们回来了
We're back somehow.
其他人呢
Where's the others?
波琳
Pauline?
我不知道这是怎么回事  莱尔
I don't know about this, Lyle!
山姆
Sam?
莱尔
Lyle?
梅兰妮
Melanie?
这是一切开始的地方
This is where it began.
也是一切结束的地方
And this is where it ends.
对我们所有人来说
For all of us.
我不明白
I don't understand.
告诉我你是什么意思
Tell me what you mean.
你们没事吧
Hey! You guys okay?
莱尔呢
Yeah. Where's Lyle?
他在我前面
He was ahead of me.
天啊  如果他没能过来呢
Oh, my God, what if he didn't make it?
走吧
Come on.
穿过来时
Like, coming through...
你们有没有看见什么
...did any of you guys see stuff?
-我什么也没看见  -我看见了
- I couldn't see crap. - I did.
像是一段回忆
Like a memory.
我看到的是预言
Mine was like a premonition.
莱尔应该过来了  但他没来
Lyle should've been there, but he wasn't.
你留在这里等他
You stay here and wait for him.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
去找我儿子
To get my son.
我要去找茱莉亚
I'm gonna go find Julia.
大家都得保持低调  好吗
Everybody needs to keep a low profile, all right?
如果镇上有人看见我们回来了
Anyone in this town sees that we're back,
就会引起大骚乱的
and it's gonna cause chaos.
等我想出计划再来找你
Once I come up with a plan, I'll find you.
亨特
Hunter?
别惹麻烦
Stay out of trouble.
低调
Lay low.
我跟你一起去
I'm coming with you.
-我想见小詹姆斯  -不
- I want to see Junior. - No.
我必须一个人去做
I have to do this alone.
你得留在这里找到莱尔  拜托了
You need to stay here and find Lyle, please.
我们回来了  不管要发生什么事  我们都需要莱尔
Now that we're back, whatever's gonna happen, we need Lyle.
真不敢相信我过来了
I can't believe I made it through.
现在我真的在切斯特磨坊镇
Now I'm really here in Chester's Mill.
系好安全带  孩子
Buckle up, kid.
事情会变得更为诡异的
It's about to get a lot weirder.
最危险的地方
No better place to hide
就是最安全的地方
than right under my dad's nose.
这里好安静
It's so peaceful down here.
我们该走了
We should get going.
我们能不能
Can we just...
在这里躺一会儿
lie here for a little while?
享受宁静
Enjoy the peacefulness?
这会让我觉得没那么孤独
It would help me feel less alone.
波琳
Pauline?